

MICHAŁ ULISZAK

A Self-starter wiling to enter IT industry.

+48 794521626

michal.uliszak@gmail.com

Os. Platynowe, Goślinowo, Poland

66.03.1989

Education

Highschool Diploma Gniezno, Poland 2006-2008

Skills

C#
.NET
Entity Framework
SQL
CRM
Driving License (B)
Microsoft Office

Languages

Polish Native Speaker

> English Advanced

PROFILE

The work I performed required communication skills, great flexibility and quick problem solving. Thanks to them, I am not afraid of new challenges and developed my interpersonal skills. Recently I found great pleasure in coding. I started to learn from youtube videos and decided to buy few udemy courses. I chose C#, because it used in game development but now I'm making my first own WebAPI in ASP.NET, using Entity Framework and SQL DataBase.

I'm testing my own code, learnt that from codewars.com, and it can be the best way for me to start my adventure with IT. Manual or Automatic? No problem, I want to learn and start that journey!

Of course everything is on beginner level, I don't have real experience, but I'm using best practises like dependency injection, SOLID or DRY.

Experience

Customer Service Consultant

PGNiG OD Sp. z o.o. | Gniezno/Poznań | 2017 - now comprehensive service for individual and non-consumer customers, concluding contracts, handling settlements, archiving documents, selling products

- concluding contracts and customer service in CRM
- JIRA/Sap but only from customer perspective
- handling customer settlements in few billing programs
- Trainings in soft skills, self-improvement, selling
- selling additional products (insurances, healthcare service)

Salesman/Sports equipment service technician

Intersport Polska | Poznań | 2015 - 2017

active sales in the store, service and repair of sports equipment provided by customers (not only purchased in the store), warranty services, inventory, minor repairs in the store, warehouse works

Contact Center Consultant

PGNiG OD Sp. z o.o. | Poznań | 2013 - 2015

comprehensive telephone and e-mail service for individual clients and non-consumers.